<resources>
    <string name="app_name">S.T.A.L.K.E.R. Factions</string>

    <string name="lonDesc">Loners are a nomadic semi-unified group of Stalkers who simply live off
        the Zone in order to earn some coin for their daily lives. Loners are neutral toward almost
        all other factions, but do have complications with the Military, and, to a lesser extent,
        the Mercenaries, and openly oppose the Bandit faction for their actions against free
        Stalkers. Most Loners are only concerned with the riches of the Zone, and do not pay
        attention to the other factions\' hatred for each other - provided, of course, they do not
        threaten them. Because of this, Loners are often recruited by various factions as mercenaries.</string>

    <string name="monDesc">The Monolith were originally ordinary Stalkers who believed in the power
        of the Wish Granter. Prior to Clear Sky, the faction reportedly made an exodus to the
        Zone\'s center and disappeared. After the large emission during the events of
        S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Clear Sky, they became active. The Monolith are the front line soldiers
        of the C-Consciousness, and would rather die than let any Stalker reach the sacred crystal.
        Although capable of higher reasoning and emotion, they nevertheless carry out orders with
        fanatic effectiveness. The Monolith faction has no allies, and actively attacks all other
        factions.</string>

    <string name="milDesc">The Ukrainian military supposedly has the Zone contained in order to
        prevent the looting of dangerous, radioactive materials and to prevent the unauthorized
        entering of any individuals. They allegedly enforce this rule with a "Shoot-on-sight"
        declaration.</string>

    <string name="merDesc">The Mercenaries are a private military force operating within the Zone.
        They are professional soldiers who will do just about anything in the Zone, ranging from
        retrieval, assassinations, body-guarding, etc. Though, of course, it must be for the right
        price. Mercenaries are usually neutral toward other factions, as they are a source of
        income, unless they interfere with their operations.</string>

    <string name="freDesc">Freedom is a clan of stalkers who fight for free access to the Zone,
        and their views are somewhat anarchistic, believing nobody can own the Zone and seeing
        it both as a scientific marvel and as a free life inside the Zone\'s borders. In contrast
        to the regimented, highly disciplined atmosphere of Duty, the members of Freedom have a
        much more relaxed, informal attitude. They appear to have a more casual command structure,
        often referring to each other as "bro", with a number of members shown making regular
        recreational use of alcohol and marijuana. This further reflects their status as a clan of
        like-minded free spirits, unlike the ex-military soldiers of Duty.</string>

    <string name="ecoDesc">The Ecologists are Ukrainian scientists sent into the Zone on behalf of
        the government, but seem to be affiliated with outside organizations (namely, foreign
        governments who, knowing how dangerous the Zone is, and with their own goals towards the
        Zone\'s materials, are willing to pay more to the Ecologists than the Ukranian government
        does). Their main purpose is the study of all aspects of the Zone, using scientific methods
        to further explain what the Zone is, and its purpose. The Ecologists are neutral to all
        factions, and are not involved in any of their conflicts. Due to the military\'s slipping g
        rip on the Zone, the Ecologists rely on opportunistic Dutyers, Loners, and Mercenaries to
        provide them protection, and to perform errands that may require combat, since the
        scientists are better thinkers than fighters.</string>

    <string name="dutDesc">Duty was founded by former military expedition survivors and Stalkers
        concerned about the looming horrors of the Zone. They are one of the largest Stalker clans
        in the Zone. They have a strict military code (such as no smoking, maintaining one\'s weapons
        , etc...) and operate in a military fashion, using ranks like Sergeant, Major, Captain, and
        General. Their goal is to contain and destroy the Zone, fearing that it will spread to the
        outside world.</string>

    <string name="cleDesc">Clear Sky is the most secretive faction within the Zone. The faction was
        disbanded after losing the majority of their manpower during the events in S.T.A.L.K.E.R.:
        Clear Sky. The Clear Sky faction was originally composed of former researchers of the
        C-Consciousness who broke away from them in order to conduct their own research on how to
        either destroy or contain the zone. The other members of the faction were ordinary stalkers
        who joined their cause for their own reasons.</string>

    <string name="banDesc">The Bandits are raiders and marauders of the Zone, ranging from petty
        thugs and gangsters to organized crime syndicates. Apart from Freedom, which treats them
        with marginal contempt, everyone hates the Bandits due to their nefarious acts of robbing
        and exploiting honest Stalkers. Most Bandits are unorganized and leaderless; there are
        only a few known Bandit leaders and camps, and even then their groups are still fairly
        disorganized, with underlings always trying to take control by overthrowing the previous
        leader.</string>
</resources>